둘 다
천천히 좀 먹어
Will you two slow down?
종업원이
뺏어가기라도 한대?
You're eating like they're going
to take it away from you.
전 자라는 아이라서요
I'm a growing girl.
이렇게 만나니
정말 좋구나
It's such a pleasure
seeing you and...
네 일도 잘 되가고
Seeing how well work is going.
네, 아주 잘 되가요
Work's going really well, yeah.
상사가
책이 완성되면
My boss said that
he wants to see my book
보고 싶대요,
진짜 흥분되요
when it's done,
which is really exciting.
그건...어떻게 돼가니?
Where are you at with that?
이제 네 챕터를
완성했고
Oh, well, I've done four
of the essays,
다듬고 있는
중이에요
and I'm just kind
of polishing them up.
아홉 챕터로
하고 싶은데
And my hope is that
it's going to be nine.
But, you know, it's a memoir.
So-- have to live them first.
자서전이라
인생을 덜 살았으니...
Tim, I
don't want to just leave it
여보, 지금 그냥
말하는게
좋겠어
till the end of dinner.
그래, 맞아, 어...
I hear that. Um...
하나,
엄마랑 나랑...
Hannah, your mother
and I have been...
상의를 해봤는데
이제 그만...
Talking, and we feel
that it may be time--
how can I phrase this?
뭐라고 해야할까...
Well, we see how well
you're doing at work.
네가 직장도 잘
다니고 있고
원하는 것도
잘 찾아가는 것 같구나
And you really seem to be figuring
out what it is that you want.
하지만 이제
마지막 지지를 해야겠다
But it may be time
for one final push.
"마지막 지지"라뇨?
What is a "final push"?
더 이상
널 지원하지 않을거야
We're not going to be
supporting you any longer.
저기, 로린,
난 그렇게
You see, I wasn't going to
phrase it like that, Loreen,
- 말 하려던게 아니야
- 난 직장도 없어요
- the way you phrased it.
- But I have no job.
하지만 지금 인턴에서
정식으로 채용된다며?
No, you have an internship that you
say is going to turn into a job.
언제일진 몰라요
I don't know when.
2년 전에
대학 졸업을 했고
You graduated from
college two years ago.
지금까지 지원을 했으니
그걸로 충분해
We've been supporting you for
two years, and that's enough.
지금 경제가
얼마나 안 좋은지 아세요?
Do you know how crazy
the economy is right now?
I mean, all my friends
get help from their parents.
친구들도 다
부모님 도움 받아요
그래, 다 알지
We are sympathetic to that.
전 외동딸이잖아요
But I'm your only child,
제가 전 재산을
탕진하는 것도 아니고...
it's not like I'm draining
all your resources.
갑자기
왜 이러시는 거예요?
I mean, this feels
very arbitrary.
우리 사정도
모르잖니?
You don't know anything
about our finances.
우린 교수란다, 하나,
교수!
We're professors, Hannah.
Professors.
네 럭셔리한 생활에
발 맞출수가 없구나
We can't keep bankrolling
your groovy lifestyle.
"럭셔리"한 생활이요?
My "groovy" lifestyle?
한 두개가 아냐,
렌트비에
The bills add up.
We're covering your rent,
보험료에
휴대폰 비용까지
your insurance,
your cell phone.
가족 요금으로 하면
싸다면서요
You said it was cheaper for you
if I was on the family plan.
그렇지
Yeah.
더 필요하신거
있으세요?
May I get you more of anything?
- 어...
- 아뇨, 됐어요
- Uh--
- No, she's fine.
- 맛있네요
- 네
- Delicious.
- Yeah.
말도 안 되요
This is nuts.
테드, 좀 거들어요
Ted, can you help me here?
내가 약쟁이가 안 된것 만으로도
행운인줄 아셔야 되요
I could be a drug addict.
Do you realize how lucky you are?
I mean, it doesn't have
to be heroin,
헤로인 까지는
아니더라도
it could be something more
insidious, like pills.
알약처럼
미묘한 것들 말예요
Which are legal, and which a
lot of kids do, all the time.
합법인데다
모든 애들이 항상 하는거죠
그렇게 천천히
완전 맛이 가죠
And then slowly they
become totally useless.
쌩쌩 돌아가는 것 같다
망가져요
They seem really high-functioning,
and then it just ruins them.
Okay, my friend Sophie, her
parents don't support her.
내 친구 소피도
혼자 먹고 살아요
지난 여름에
낙태를 두 번 했는데
Last summer, she had
two abortions
연달아서요,
아무도 오지 않았죠
right in a row,
and no one came with her.
그 말은
왜 하는거야?
What does that have
to do with anything?
그러니까
내 꿈에 거의 다다랐다고요
I'm just saying that I am so
close to the life that I want,
부모님도 원했었죠
the life that you want for me,
근데 이제 와서
포기하라고요?
for you to just end
that right now?
이제 돈은 못 줘
No more money.
- 언제부터요?
- 지금부터
- Starting when?
- Starting now.
내일 더 얘기하자
We can talk about it tomorrow.
내일 또
보기 싫어요
I don't want to
see you tomorrow.
- 뭐?
- 화요일이면 가는데?
- What?
- But we fly out Tuesday.
I have work, and then
I have a dinner thing,
일도 있고
저녁 약속도 있고
그 담엔 바빠요
and then I am busy
내 자신을
찾느라요
trying to become who I am.
번역 - ☆아하하☆
(mfkd2017@gmail.com)
알람 울려
Alarm, alarm.
- 어딨어?
- 몰라
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
아가씨, 다 왔어요
Miss? You are here.
벌써요?
Already?
좋은 아침, 찰리
Good morning, Charlie.
왜 안 깨웠어?
Why didn't you wake me up?
하나 방에서
자버렸잖아
I didn't mean to sleep
with Hannah.
둘이 마치
천사같아서
Because you
two looked so angelic.
음, 쟨 빅토리아 시크릿 천사고
난 비만 아기 천사겠네
Hmm, Victoria's secret angel,
fat baby angel.
- Don't say that.
- No way, you look awesome these days.
- 말도 안 되
- 아냐, 너 요즘 끝내줘
쳐다보지마
Please avert your eyes.
아...
Oh...
선물이야?
Is that a present?
나를 위해?
Is that for me?
- 그래, 이리 줘
- 고마워
- Uh-oh. Give it here.
- Thank you.
또 매리 타일러 무어 쇼
보다 잤지?
You guys fell asleep to Mary
Tyler Moore again, huh?
응, 들켰네
Yes, guilty.
벽 넘어로 들으면
진짜 이상해
It's a very odd show
to hear through a wall.
내가 간다
Coming at ya.
다 왔다
Here it comes.
팡!
Pow!
금방 너한테
키스 날렸어
I just blew up a kiss on you.
- 타월 안 벗어?
- 응
- Are you going to leave your towel on?
- Yes.
난 네 몸 한번도 못 봤고
넌 내 몸 항상 보잖아
But I never see you naked,
and you always see me naked.
솔직히 그 반대여야
하는데
When it should actually
be the other way around.
- 너 예뻐, 그만해
- 그런거 필요없어
- You are beautiful, shut up.
- I don't need that.
- 네 가슴만 보면 되
- 미안하지만 싫어
- I need to see your boobs.
- We, you don't get to, sorry.
난 섹스 상대에게만
내 가슴 보여줘
I only show my boobs to people
I'm having sex with.
걔 피하려고
내 방에서 잤잖아
You literally slept
in my bed to avoid him.
알아
I know.
우린 모든걸
다 겪었어
He and I have turned a corner.
걔가 만지는건
마치
His touch now feels like
추수감사절날 내 무릎에 얹은
변태 삼촌의 손같아
a weird uncle just putting his
hand on my knee at Thanksgiving.
어떻게 할거야?
What are you going to do?
- 끝내버리려고
- 그러면 안 되
- I think I have to end it.
- You can't do that.
해야 되, 왜 안 되?
I have to.
Why not?
창문 밖에서
라디오들고 있을거니까
'Cause he'll stand outside
our window with a boom box
- 아님 자살하든가
- 그만해
- or he'll kill himself.
- Stop.
안녕, 자기
아, 이런
Hey, babe.
Oh, whoa.
미안, 내 여친만
있는 줄 알았어
Sorry. I thought it was
just my girlfriend in here.
야, 항상 우린
여기 같이 있거든?
Dude, it's never just
your girlfriend in here.
인사하려고
그런거야
I'm just saying goodbye.
둘다 밤에 봐,
와인 사올게
I'll see you ladies tonight,
and I'll pick up wine.
그럼, 키스 받아
Okay, big kisses.
잘 가
Bye.
저렇게 사랑받으면
기분이 어때?
What does it even feel like
to be loved that much?
몰라,
아무것도 안 느껴져
I don't know.
I can't feel it anymore.
아, 안 되
Oh, no.
알아, 그냥...
I know, I just--
나쁜 년이 된
기분이야
And it makes me feel
like such a bitch
너무 잘해주는게
느껴지니까
'cause I can feel him
being so nice to me.
한편으론
정말 화도 나고
And yet it makes me so angry.
너 이것만은
인정해야 겠다
I think you need to admit
something to yourself,
쟤 오럴 해주는게
질린거야
which is that you're sick
of eating him out.
- 으웩
- 남성성이 전혀 없거든
- Ew.
- 'Cause he has a vagina.
- 안녕
- 봉쥬르, 룸메
- Hi. Ca va?
- Bonjour, roomie.
- 너도!
- 세상에, 멋있어서 토 나와
Oh, my God.
You're so hip, I could puke.
그 모자 난 진짜 안 어울리는데
넌 진짜 멋있다!
I can never pull off that hat.
How do you pull off that hat?
네 잠바도 예뻐
I love your jumper.
피부도
무섭게 아름다워
Your skin is, like,
hauntingly beautiful.
- 짐 풀어도 될까?
- 뭐?
- Can I put my bags down?
- What?
아, 이런, 물론이지
Oh, my God, of course.
사촌 중에
네가 젤 좋아
You're like my favorite cousin.
영국인 사촌있는건
친구들 중 나뿐이야
I'm the only one of my girlfriends
that has a British cousin.
얼마동안 지낼거야?
How long do you think
you're going to stay for?
싫어서 묻는거 아냐,
원하면 계속 있어도 되
Not that I'm asking you to leave.
You can totally stay forever if you want to.
- 뭐 좀 먹어도 될까?
- 물론
- Can I have something to eat?
- Yeah.
거기서 1년간
인턴했잖아
You've been interning
there for a year.
이제 월급달라고
얘기해
You need to tell them
it's time to get paid.
이렇게 불쌍해 보여도
돈은 들지
Costs a lot of money
to look this cheap.
농담아냐,
네가 집세 못 내면
This is not a joke. If you can't
afford to pay your half of the rent,
찰리가 이사올거라고
Charlie is going
to move in here.
- 찰리 찰거니까
- 그런 말 안 했어
- You're dumping Charlie.
- I didn't say that.
아담한테 밤에 오라고 문자했는데
답이 없어
So I texted Adam about tonight, and
I have not heard anything back.
하나, 나 봐
Hannah, look at me.
걘 절대 답 안 해
He never, ever texts you back.
전화해야하나?
Maybe I should call him.
문자가 가장 하위의
소통 수단이라고 네가 그랬잖아
Didn't you say texting's like the
lowest form of communication
- 대화 기둥에서?
- 대화 상이야
- on the pillar of chat?
- The totem of chat.
아냐, 페이스북이
제일 낮고
No, the lowest,
that would be Facebook,
다음에 구글 채팅,
그리고 문자
followed by gChat,
then texting,
- 이메일, 전화야
- 알았어
- then email, then phone.
- Gotcha.
직접 만나는게 이상적이지만
요즘엔 어렵지
Face-to-face is, of course, ideal.
But it's not of this time.
좋아, 그럼 어떻게
직접 만나지?
Okay, but then how am I supposed
to get him face-to-face
문자 답을
안 하잖아?
if he refuses to text me?
제사가 환영 파티를
진짜 좋아할거야
Think Jessa will really appreciate
the welcome-home dinner.
진정한 친구다운
행동이지
It's a very friendish
thing of us to do.
왜?
What?
또 늦게
나타나겠지
I just know she's
going to show up late,
그리스 시장에서 산
wearing some fabulous
blankety dress
화려하고 치렁치렁한
드레스를 입고 와선
from a Grecian marketplace
and be like...
"어, 어디서 샀는지
기억이 안 나네?"하겠지
"Oh, I can't
remember where I got this."
걔가 돌아와서
정말 기쁘다고
I'm really glad that
she's coming home.
제사가
돌아올때마다
But every time she
comes into town,
넌 술에 취해 있다가
you go on some
week-long bender,
다음 나라로
여행 떠나면
and then she leaves to go
off to her next country
내가 남아서
뒷처리를 해야하지
and I'm left to
pick up the pieces.
좋아, 나
이런 말 잘 안 하지만
Okay, it is so rare
that I say this,
걔가 쿨하다고
생각할 뿐이야
but I just think she's fun.
그래, 캐롤린 남친이랑
섹스한 것도 쿨했었지
Yeah, it was really fun when she
fucked Carolyn’s boyfriend.
네 남친이랑은
안 했잖아
She didn't fuck your boyfriend.
그 학기에
찰리가 프라하 갔었으니까
That's 'cause he was
in Prague that semester.
고마워요
Thanks so much.
놀리타 지역에
이 가격은 엄청난거야
It's a great deal for Nolita.
I mean 2,100 a month?
Amaze.
한 달에 210이라니?
놀랍삼!
기숙사보단
좀 비싸지만
It's a little more
expensive than the dorms,
아일린 숙모는
우리에게 완벽한 아파트래
but aunt Ilene thinks it's like
the perfect bachelorette pad.
알지?
I mean...
포스터 맘에 들어?
Do you like the poster?
어, 그게,
저 영화 본 적 없어
Oh, you know, I've never
seen that movie.
- 드라마만 봤구나?
- 드라마야?
- Only the show?
- Is it a show?
세상에,
장난하는거지?
Oh, my God.
You're not serious.
그건 페이스북
안 하는 것과 같아
I mean, that's like not
being on Facebook.
- 페이스북 안 해
- 너 존나 고급스럽다
- I'm not on Facebook.
- You're so fucking classy.
참 희한해,
넌 물론 캐리같지만
You know, you're funny because
you're definitely like a Carrie
사만사 같은 면도 있고
머리는 샬롯이야
but with, like, some Samantha
aspects and Charlotte hair.
- 진짜 훌륭한 조합이야
- 아, 고마워
- That's like a really good combination.
- Oh, thank you.
난 속으론
물론 캐리이지만
I think I'm definitely
a Carrie at heart,
가끔은...
but, like, sometimes--
가끔 사만사가
튀어 나오기도 해
sometimes Samantha
kind of comes out.
학교에 있을땐
미란다처럼 행동하려고 하지
And then when I'm at school, I definitely
try and put on my Miranda hat.
프랑스 전엔
어디 있었어?
Where were you before France?
프랑스 전엔
암스테르담에 있었고...
Before France,
I was in Amsterdam--
아니, 발리에 있었어
No, I was in Bali,
거기서 진주를 캤어
and I was
shucking pearls there.
그리고 서퍼를 만났어
And then I met a surfer--
세상에,
널 좋아했겠다?
Oh, my God.
Did he really like you?
- 널 많이 좋아했지?
- 응, 많이 좋아했어
- He really liked you, right?
- Yeah, he really liked me.
- 하나구나?
- 안녕하세요, 알리스터
- Hannah?
- Hello, Alistair.
안녕하세요
Hello.
할 말 있구나
You seem eager.
아시다시피 제가
1년 넘게 여기서 일했어요
As you know, I've been working
here for over a year.
그렇게 오래됐나?
Has it been that long?
자긴 우리 회사의
소중한 자산이야
Well, you are an invaluable
part of our operation.
최근에 안건데 그게
쓸모없는거에 비하면
Which I recently learned
means very valuable
굉장히 소중하단
뜻이라면서요?
as opposed to not
at all valuable.
그리고 제 상황이
좀 바뀌어서요
And I wanted to let you know that
my circumstances have changed
월급을 받아야
일 할 수 있겠네요
and I can no longer afford
to work for free.
이런, 하나
Oh, Hannah.
떠나게 되서
정말 슬프구나
I am so sorry to lose you.
회사 트위터를
자기한테 맡기려 했는데
I was just going to start
you manning our Twitter,
트위터에 알맞는
위트를 가졌잖아
you have just the
quippy voice for that.
아뇨, 떠나는거 아녜요
Oh, no, I'm not quitting.
그게, 조이-린도
인턴 후 채용됐으니
I just-- I know that Joy-Lynn
got hired after interning,
- 저도 그렇게...
- 하나
- so I thought that maybe--
- Hannah.
조이-린은
포토샵을 할줄알아
Joy-Lynn knows Photoshop.
지금 경제에
Now, in this economy,
매일 몇 번의
인턴직 의뢰가 오는 줄 아니?
do you know how many internship
requests I get every day?
- 아마도 많겠죠?
- 50번 정도야
- I would assume a lot.
- 50, it's about 50.
솔직히 다
스팸에다 넣어버려
I practically route them
into my spam folders.
그러니 여기서
배울게 없다고 생각되면...
So, if you think you have just
nothing left to learn from us...
아뇨, 그런 거
아녜요, 정말요
No, it is not that, really.
그게, 먹고는
살아야 하니까요
I just, you know, gotta eat.
글쎄,
더 배고파지면
Well, when you get
hungry enough,
방법을 찾게 되겠지
you're going to figure it out.
신체적으로요,
아님 일에 고프다고요?
Do you mean like physically
hungry or hungry for the job?
네 에너지가
그리울거다
I am really going
to miss your energy.
너한테 정말
잘 된 일이야
I think this is going
to be really good for you.
어, 그 때
제 책 완성하면
Uh, you mentioned that when
I was finished with my book,
보내시라고
하셨죠?
I could send it to you.
어, 그 책을
네가 검토할텐데
Well, we wouldn't have you here
네가 나가버렸으니
어떻하겠니?
to read it for us.
Would we?
어디 가?
Where are you going?
에너지 바
사다 줄래?
Will you get me a luna bar?
스마트 워터랑
비타민 워터도?
And a smartwater
and vitaminwater?
너, 안녕
Yo, hey.
아니, 지금
친구 집에서 나왔어
Yeah, no, I'm actually
just leaving a friend's house
네 집 바로 근처라...
that's, like, right
by your house, so...
그래?
Yeah?
- 왔어, 예쁜이
- 안녕
- Hey. Hey, doll.
- Hey.
아빠도 "예쁜이"라고
부르는데
"Doll," that is what
my dad calls me.
그래, 들어서 알아,
같은 자위 클럽이었거든
Yeah, I know. He told me.
We're in the same circle jerk.
- 오늘 최악이야
- 근처에 있었어?
- I just had the worst ever day.
- You were nearby?
왜?
Why?
어, 회사에서 잘렸어
Um, I got fired from my job.
인턴이었잖아?
Weren't you an intern?
얼마동안 일 했으니
따지자면 인턴인거지
Well, I was working there for a while
so I was technically an intern.
그러니까 더 이상
거기서 못 노는거네?
So basically they just asked you
to not hang out there anymore?
하지만
여기 와서...
But I was walking over here--
재밌냐?
충격먹고 여기 오다가
Funny. I was on my way over
here and I was panicking,
이렇게 생각했어,
영문학 전공이니까 그걸로...
but then it occurred to me, I'm an
English major, there has to be some--
전공따위,
난 비교문학 전공인데 개뿔도 소용없어
Major doesn't matter.
I was comp lit and it hasn't done shit.
넌 배우니까
문학 비교하고 안 그래?
Yeah, but you're an actor, so aren't you
always comparing different literature?
모, 몰라
I-I don't know.
이제 나무 일에 빠졌어,
덜 가식적이라
Plus I'm into this woodworking stuff.
It's just more honest.
그래, 다 멋있네,
연극은 어쩌고?
Yeah, it all looks awesome.
But what about your play?
아, 안 할거야,
그 자식이 싸가지라
Yeah, we're not doing it.
That guy's a dick.
- 앉아도 될까?
- 응
- Can I sit down?
- Yeah.
뭐 하나 말해 줄건데
욕 하지 않을래?
So if I tell you something, will you
promise that you won't judge me?
그래
Yes.
어제까지
부모님한테 용돈 타 썼어
Till yesterday, I got all of
my money from my parents.
알았어
Okay.
정 떨어져서
말도 하기 싫지?
Does that make you feel sick?
Make you not want to talk to me?
아니, 내 부모님이야 머저리라서
한 푼도 받기 싫지만
No, I mean I wouldn't take shit from my parents.
They're buffoons.
- 할머니가 달마다 8십 만원씩 주셔
- 우와!
- But my grandma gives me $800 a month.
- Whoa.
그래
Mm-hmm.
그럼 그걸로
먹고 사는거야?
So is, like, that how
you support yourself?
응, 다른 일도
좀 하고...
Yeah.
I mean, I supplement.
하지만 덕분에
노예 짓은 안 해도 되니까
But it gives me the freedom that I
don't have to be anyone's slave.
넌 어느 인간의 노예도 되면
안 되
You should never be
anyone's fucking slave.
나만 빼고
Except mine.
꽤 흥분되나봐?
You're feeling pretty frisky.
그 표현 증오해
진짜 싫어해
I really despise that word.
I hate it so much.
네가 정말 좋아,
어디로 사라질거야?
I like you so much.
I don't know where you disappear to.
무슨 소리야?
나 여기 있어
What are you talking about?
I'm right here.
아직 밝다니
이상하네
It's so funny that
it's still light out,
요즘엔 훨씬 빨리
어두워 지던데
but it's getting dark
a lot earlier these days.
- 네가 쓴 시야?
- 됐어, 나쁜 놈아
- Is this some of your poetry?
- Don't be a jerk.
내가?
Who, me?
이력서에
그런 칸 알아?
Do you know that part
on your resume
특별한 재주
써 넣는 곳?
where they ask you to list
all of your special skills?
일 안 구한지
존나 오래돼서 몰라
I haven't applied for a job
in a long fucking time.
이런거
쓰는 칸이야
It's the thing where they
ask you to list, like,
요가, 스페인어
yoga, Spanish,
수상스키, 포토샵
waterskiing, Photoshop.
근데 난...
I feel like I...
특별한 재주가
없는 것 같아
Don't have any special skills.
- 할 수 있는거 있어
- 뭐?
- I have something you can do.
- What?
하지만 먼저
조건에 맞는지 봐야겠어
But first I have to see if you
fulfill all the requirements.
조건이 뭔데?
What are the requirements?
배 대고 누워 봐
Lie on your stomach.
- 지금?
- 그래, 지금, 잠깐
- Now?
- Yes, now. Wait.
현대 직장 여성 당신이
좋아하는걸 알지
You modern career woman,
I know what you like.
여기 이렇게 와서
You think you can just
come in here
그런 말을 해도 된다고
생각해?
and talk all that noise?
어, 아니
Uh, no.
다리를 잡아
Grab your legs.
- 뭐라고 한거야?
- 다리 잡으라고
- Just-- what did you say?
- Grab your legs.
좋아
Okay.
그래, 좋았어
Okay, this is good.
- 윤활제 가져올게
- 그건 뭐하려고?
- I'm gonna go get some lube.
- Why do we need to get lube?
왔을 때
그 자세 그대로 있어야 되
When I get back, I want you
in the exact same position,
다른 것들은
다 벗고
but take all the rest
of the shit off.
콘돔 가져올래?
Will you get a condom?
생각해볼게
I'll consider it.
존나 이런
Jesus fucking Christ.
벗기가 힘들어
This is really hard.
- 이러면 되?
- 응
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- 콘돔 하고있어?
- 아니!
- You putting on a condom?
- No!
- 뭐, 하고있지?
- 응
- Wait, you are, right?
- Yes.
좋아, 왜냐면
윤활제라고 해서
Okay, 'cause when you
said the thing about lube,
네가 그걸 할까봐
걱정했거든
I was worried you were
going to try to--
do that.
Please don't do that.
제발 그거 하지마
끔찍하거든,
고마워
That feels awful.
Thank you.
- 괜찮아
- 그래, 고마워
- It's all right.
- Okay. Thank you.
똑바로 넣었어
That's the right spot.
응, 미안
Yeah, sorry.
그럼 이 상태로
좀 있는거야?
So I can just stay like
this for a little while?
응
Yeah.
- 내가 좀 움직일까?
- 뭐?
- Do you need me to move more?
- What?
내가 혹시
이렇게 움직여줬음 하나해서
I just didn't know if you wanted
me to be more like-- like that.
아냐, 괜찮아,
잘 하고 있어
Oh, no. This is fine.
You're doing great.
이렇게만 하면 되
This is all you need to do.
다른 구멍 얘기한거
미안해
I'm sorry about the
wrong hole thing.
그게, 지금은
하기 싫었어
I just-- I don't want
to do it now,
만약 한다면
상의를 하고 싶어
and if we did, I'd just
want to talk about it
알아내서...그게,
난 좀 불편해서...
and just figure out what-- it's
just not comfortable for me--
- 그냥 조용히 하자
- 화난거 아니지?
- Let's play the quiet game.
- So you're not mad at me?
응, 다 좋아
No, I'm great.
좋은 시간이야
A great time.
정신나간거
해볼까?
You know
what would be crazy?
- 그게 뭔데?
- 우리가...
- What would be crazy?
- If we...
지금 여기서
하는거야
Just got crazy,
right here right now.
해보는 거야
We could just do that.
방해물도 없고
아무도 없어
Nobody's stopping us.
Nobody's home.
지금 뭐가
가장 흥분될 것 같아?
What would turn you
on the most right now?
날 가장 흥분시키는거?
What would turn me on the most?
넌 뭐가 흥분되는데?
What would turn you on the most?
널 흥분시키는게
날 흥분시켜
To turn you on, that's what
would turn me on.
- 바로 그걸 하자
- 좋아, 어...
- Let me do that.
- Okay, uh...
낯선 사람이
되는건 어때?
Um, what if you
were a stranger?
그래, 낯선 사람
Oh, yeah, a stranger.
완전 다른 사람이
되는 거야
What if you were just like
a totally different person?
너처럼
행동을 안 하고
You didn't act like you?
제사가 왔나봐
I think Jessa's here.
- 아니, 레이일거야
- 레이 초대했어?
- Oh, no. I think that might be Ray.
- You invited Ray?
- 네 사람 밖에 없으니까
- 저녁 먹는거니까
- It was going to be like a four-person party.
- That's called dinner.
이런, 미안해
Gosh, I'm sorry.
- 그 문신은 다 뭐야?
- 무슨 말이야?
- What's with all the tattoos?
- What do you mean?
그런거 다
왜 했어?
Why'd you do all of them?
거의 동화책 그림들이야
They're illustrations from
children's books mostly.
엉덩이에 있는 것도?
Even the one on your ass?
아니, 그건
내 친구 제사가 한거야
Uh, no. That one
my friend Jessa did
2학년 때
옷핀으로
sophomore year
with a safety pin.
달을 감고있는
뱀이지
It's a snake wrapped
around the moon.
언제 한거야?
When did you do that?
거의 고등학교 때
한거야
I did them mostly
in high school.
왜?
Why?
솔직히? 갑자기
살이 왕창 쪄서
Truthfully? I gained a bunch
of weight very quickly,
내 몸의 통제를
잃어버린 듯 했어
and I just felt very out
of control of my own body,
그래서 막 이랬어
and it was just this, like,
"내 몸은
내가 통제한다!"
"I'm taking control
of my own shape."
- 나도 고등학교 때 뚱뚱했어
- 정말?
- You know, I was fat in high school.
- Really?
응, 하지만
온 몸에 그림을 그리진 않았지
Yeah, but I didn't go
drawing all over myself.
너 이제 별로 안 뚱뚱해,
레이저로 지워
You're not that fat anymore.
You can just have them lasered off.
Mm.
Mmm.
- 몇 시야?
- 어...
- What time is it?
- Um...
5시
5:00.
몇 시야?
What time is it?
9시 45분
9:45.
저녁 약속에
완전 늦었어
I am so late
for this dinner thing.
씨발
Fuck.
진심으로
정말 정말 좋았어
Seriously, this was
really, really nice.
만나서 정말 좋았어
It was really good to see you.
응, 나도,
와줘서 고마워
Well, I'm glad.
Thanks for coming.
훨씬 기분이 나아졌어...
It made me feel
a lot better, so...
다시 만날까?
I'll see you soon?
응, 문자해
Yeah, just text me.
이게 지령은 아니지만
대체적으로
It's not like they're commandments,
but generally speaking,
25살 이하랑은
데이트 안 하는게 내 법이야
as a general rule, I try not to
date women that are under 25
드러머랑 한 번이라도
성교를 한 여자 역시 안 되
or that have been at one point in
their life penetrated by a drummer.
- 한 번이었어!
- 얜 다 해당되
- One time!
- Guilty of both.
그런데 오늘 아침
가게를 갔다가
But I was walking through
the mall this morning,
저 두개의 커다란 녹색 눈알이
동동 떠다니는걸 본거야
I see these two huge green
orbs bobbing through the mall.
- 봐! 저런 눈 본 적 있어?
- 내 눈 맞아!
- Look at these eyes! Have you seen these eyes?
- They're my eyes!
- 정말 다정해
- 너무 놀라워
- He's so nice to me.
- Ridiculous.
속눈썹도 봐,
저런거 처음 보지?
Look at those lashes, too.
Have you seen these lashes?
- 이래서 미안해
- 정말 귀여워
- Guilty as charged.
- So cute.
너 괜찮아?
You okay?
응, 하나가
안 와서 그래
Yeah, I just can't believe
Hannah didn't show up.
우리가 있잖아,
신나게 분위기 살리고!
We're here. Livin' it up.
Partyin' down.
요즘 입맛이 없어서 그런거니
기분 나빠하지마
I don't mean to be rude.
I'm just not really into eating this week.
환영 파티는
자기가 하자고 해놓곤
Hannah was the one
saying this was our big reunion
나타나지도
않잖아
and now she's
nowhere to be found.
걱정되?
어디 연락 해볼까?
Are you worried?
Should we call someone?
아니,
어딨는지 정확히 알아
No, especially because I
know exactly where she is.
그 동물이랑
변태 섹스 중일거야
She's off having gross sex
with that animal.
어떻게 변태적인데?
In what [Ay, gross?
최소한 섹스 얘기라도
듣고 싶나봐
Charlie would like to at
least hear about some sex.
- 뭐라고?
- 그냥 독려하려는거야
- Excuse me?
- Ray's just being motivational.
그래도 제사가
안 왔으니 다행이잖아
Come on, at least you didn't have
to entertain Jessa on her own.
그래, 아무도
안 온것만 빼면
Yeah, 'cause I didn't
get to entertain anybody
무지 다행이긴 하지
because no one came.
- 하나! 마르니!
- 누구야? 영국 발음인데?
- Hannah! Marnie!
- Who's that? She sounds British.
아, 미안한데
내가 창녀를 불렀어
Oh, I ordered a few hookers,
if you guys don't mind.
불가리아 여자로,
최상급이야
Bulgarian girls. Top-shelf.
- 괜찮은 애들이야
- 진짜 기발해, 정말로
- Nice girls.
- He kills me. I swear to God.
마르니!
Marnie!
젤 위에 열어
Top lock!
♪ God, she's fine,
fine, fine... ♪
파리는 꼭 가봐야 되
Paris is really
where you should be.
친불파라면...
If you're a francophile like...
- 물론 너랑 난 그렇지
- 그래
- Me and you, obviously.
- Yeah.
- 그렇다면 꼭 가야지
- 꼭 가야 되!
- Then you've got to go to France.
- You have to go.
애들 세명이 있는
집에 살며 가르쳤는데
I was a live-in educator
for these three children,
셋 다 노래를 했어
and they all sang.
걔네 아빠는
훌륭한 반전가였어
And their father was a
brilliant pacifist thinker.
그거
"사운드 오브 뮤직" 아니야?
Isn't that the plot to
"The Sound of Music"?
- 맞아
- 우리도 여행 다니자
- It is.
- We really want to travel more.
- 그냥 가면 되
- 바로 가는거야
- We could just go.
- Up and go.
너무 늦었서
정말 미안해
I am so sorry I'm so late.
- 정신없는 하나
- 와서 얘기 좀 해봐
- Hannah banana.
- Would you please come here and talk to us?
안녕
Hello.
왔구나, 왔어,
안녕
You're here.
You're here. Hi.
어떻게 지냈어?
정말 예쁘다
What's going on?
You look beautiful.
- 뭐라고?
- 뭐하는 거야?
- What'd you say?
- What's going on?
- 섹스한 냄새야
- 너 아침에 샤워했잖아
- She smells like sex.
- No, but you showered this morning.
계산을 해 봤더니
뉴욕에서
So I calculated,
and I can last in New York
사흘 반동안
살 수 있어
for 3 1/2 more days.
점심 안 먹으면
일주일 정도?
Maybe seven if
I don't eat lunch.
네 재능에 걸맞는
일을 찾아줄게
I'm going to find you a job
worthy of your talents.
글쎄, 말은 고맙지만
Well, I appreciate that,
그렇게 빨리
직장을 찾을 수 있겠어?
but I don't know how you're going
to find a job fast enough.
맥도날드에서
일해야 할거야
I'm going to have
to work at McDonald's.
거기서 일 안해도 되
You're not going
to work at McDonald's.
맥도날드가 어때서?
거기서 꼭 일해
What's wrong with McDonald's?
You should work at McDonald's.
얼마나 좋은데,
존나 끝내준다고
It's great.
It's fucking incredible.
맥도날드가 매일
몇 명을 먹여주는데?
You know how many people
McDonald's feeds every day?
세계의 몇 명이
맥도날드에 직장을 얻고?
You know how many people
it employs around the world?
그리고 음식도 끝내준다고
Plus, they make an
incredible product, okay?
맛도 정말 훌륭해
It tastes tremendous.
싸고
존나 맛도 변함없어
It's affordable.
It's fucking consistent.
나이지리아 맥도날드에 가서
I can walk into a
McDonald's in Nigeria,
치킨 맥너겟을 시켜
order chicken McNuggets.
한 입 먹으면
어떤 맛인지 알아?
When I bite into it, you know
what it's going to taste like?
고향에 온 맛일거야
It's going to taste like home.
그게 거기서 일해야 할 이유야?
난 대학도 나왔다고
It doesn't mean I have to work there.
I went to college.
나도 대학 나왔어,
결국엔 어떻게 됐지?
Yeah, I went to college, too.
You know where it left me?
학생 융자금
5천 만원만 남았지
I have $50,000
in student loans.
그 정도 빚에
쌓여있어
That's how deep in debt I am.
미안하지만 이건 마치
"클루리스"를 보는 것 같애
I'm sorry, but watching this,
this is like watching "Clueless."
영화 아님 드라마?
The movie or the TV show?
- 너 뭐해?
- 거기서 뭐해?
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing over there?
탕을 좀 만들고 있어
I'm making a little brew.
아편 차를 만들고 있어
He's making
a tea of opium pods.
잘됐네, 아편을
우리집에 들고 오다니
Oh, cool. So you brought
opium into our apartment.
그래, 굉장히 약한 거야
Well, yeah, this stuff's
pretty mild.
네가 피우던거보다
훨씬 약한 거야
This is much milder than
the stuff you'd smoke.
합법이야,
회화 시장에서 사 온거야
It's legal. I got it down
at the flower district.
그냥 가서
살 수 있어
You can just go there
and buy the pods.
- 나 좀 해도 될까?
- 웃기지마
- Is it cool if I have a little?
- Knock yourself out.
- 나 아편 싫어해
- 그래? 뭐 좋아하는데? 코카인?
- I hate opium.
- Oh, yeah, what's your thing? Coke?
아니, 코카인 안 해
No, I never do coke.
그거 하면
팬티에 똥 싸
Every time I do coke, I shit my pants.
이런, 세상에
Oh, Jesus Christ.
- 끔찍하다
- 그렇게 되
- That's horrible.
- It happens.
- 맛이 어때?
- 달콤쌉쌀해
- What does it taste like?
- It kinda tastes like twigs.
그래, 나 마실게
Yeah, I'll have some.
안 마시는게 좋을걸?
약에 완전 민감하잖아
Maybe you shouldn't.
You're super-sensitive to drugs.
괜찮을거야, 알았지?
줘 봐
I think I'm going to be fine,
okay? Hand it over.
뜨거워
It's hot.
Oh, Jesus.
세상에!
달콤쌉쌀 안 해
This does not taste like Twix.
아냐, 달콤쌉쌀해
Not Twix, twigs.
나무 조각 처럼 말이야
Twigs, like small sticks.
사라질거면,
연락은 해야되, 알았지?
If you're going to vanish,
you have to call, okay?
응, 알았어,
이제 내 방에 갈래
Yeah, okay.
I wanna go back in there.
안 되,
얘기부터 해야 되
No, you can't.
I need to talk to you first.
부모님한테 얘기하면 되,
알았지?
All you need to do is talk
to your parents, okay?
지원해달라고
부탁해
You need to ask them
to support you
아주 조그만 더
for a little
itty-bit longer,
다른 직장
구할 때까지만
just while you look
for another job.
그리고 미래에 대한
진지함을 밝혀
And tell them that you take
your future seriously.
정말 진지하니까, 하나니까
Because you do. You're Hannah.
- 찰리 여친있어?
- 응
- Does Charlie have a girlfriend?
- Yes.
마르니가
부모님한테 얘기하래
Marnie was just saying that she feels
like I need to go and talk to my parents
직장 구할 때까지
지원해 달라고
and ask them to support
me until I get a job.
그냥 넌 아티스트라고
말해
Why don't you just tell them
that you're an artist?
확실히 얘기를 해
You just need to tell
them once and for all
'난 아티스트다!'
that you are an artist.
그냥 직장 구할거라고 해
Just tell them you're
going to get a job,
그게 훨씬 그럴듯해
that's much more convincing.
다락방에서
결핵 옮을거라고 하든가
Tell them you'll get tuberculosis
in a garret if you have to.
플로베어도
그랬다고 해
Tell them it's what
Flaubert did.
걘 좋은 본보기가 아냐
Flaubert is not
a good role model,
걔 부모님은 봤어?
and have you met her parents?
그런거
못 하게 한다고
She can't just do
the artist thing.
피카소도 했다고 해
Ll them that Picasso did it.
길에서 테잎파는
가난한 래퍼도 그랬고
Rappers who were poor and sold
their tapes in the street did it.
엘비스도 했고
믹 재거도 그랬어
It's what Elvis did.
It's what Mick Jagger did.
내 새오빠도 했어
It's what my stepbrother did.
다들 신조를
굽히지 않았다고
They all stuck to their guns.
가야 겠다
I need to go.
금방 아편 차
한 컵을 다 마셨잖아
You just drank
an entire cup of opium.
넌 멋있고 아름다워
You are gorgeous and a vision.
넌 대단한 천재야
You are a brilliant genius.
둘 다 섹시한 여신이야
Both of you are sex goddesses.
너희를 볼때면
When I look at both of you,
a Coldplay song
plays in my heart.
머릿 속에서
콜드플레이 노래가 연주 되
Bye.
잘 가
세상에, 쟤 정말
좋아보인다
God, she seems like
she's in such a good place.
Mom? Papa?
엄마? 아버지?
- 하나인가봐
- 금방 아버지라고 했어?
- I think that's Hannah.
- Did she just call me papa?
- 안녕!
- 그래, 너 여기서 뭐하냐?
- Hi!
- Oh, hey. What the heck are you doing here?
보고 싶지
않다고 했잖아
I thought you didn't want
to see us anymore.
사실, 떨쳐버릴 수
없었어요
Actually, I couldn't
bear the idea
떠나시기 전에
못 본다는 생각이요
of not seeing you
before you left town.
더 중요한건,
자, 앉아요, 늦게 미안해요
But more important--
Here, you can sit down. It's late. I'm sorry--
내 책을 갖고 왔어요
...is that I
brought you my book.
읽어 보세요
I need you to read it.
- 왜 이렇게 더워
- 좋아
- Jesus, it's hot.
- Great. Yeah.
- 그러자
- 안 더워요?
- That's fine.
- Are you boiling?
좋아, 비행기에서
읽을게
Great, we'll read it
on the plane.
아니, 지금요,
지금 읽어요
No, now. I need you
to read it now.
왜냐면...
Because...
놀라게 하고 싶진
않지만
I don't want to freak you out,
어쩌면 제가
but I think that I may be
우리 세대의
대변인일 수 있어요
the voice of my generation.
아님
그냥 평범한
Or at lease a voice
보통 사람이어도
되고요
of a generation.
Well, just read.
Don't be scared, just enjoy it
그냥 읽어요,
두려워 말고 즐기세요
나중에 하나씩
얘기하면 되니까요
'cause there's going to be plenty
for us to talk about after.
그냥 읽어 보세요
Just go for it.
얘기 좀 해
I need to talk to you.
알았어
All right.
금방 일어난 일
맘에 안 들어, 전혀
I do not like what just
went down out there. At all.
하나 얘기 하는거야?
What, with Hannah?
문제가 대체 뭔데?
I guess I just don't
understand the problem.
- 마음의 준비가 돼있어
- 약에 취해 있는데?
- She seemed ready.
- She had just gotten high.
진짜 취한 사람을
못 봤구나
I'd like for you to see
a real high person.
마르니, 그렇게
안 보살펴도 되
Marnie, you can't mother
her like that.
그런거 아냐,
재앙을 막으려는 거라고
I'm not mothering her. I'm literally
preventing a disaster from happening.
하나 소설 읽어는 봤어?
Have you even read her novel?
자서전이야,
베픈데 당연히 읽어 봤지
It's a memoir, and of course I've
read it, I'm her best friend.
'베프,
내 베프야!'
Best friend.
This is my best friend.
있잖아, 그렇게
사람을 가질 순 없어
You know,
we don't own anybody.
넌 베프의 의미를
소중히 안 여기니까
Maybe you don't respect what
a best friendship means
그런 우정을 쌓을 만큼
한 곳에 오래 머물지 않잖아
because you've never stayed in one
place long enough to have one.
마르니,
나보고 어쩌라는거야?
Marnie, I can't help
your feelings.
그럼 두 시간이나
늦은건 어때?
Maybe you can help
being two hours late
널 위해 연
저녁 모임에 말이야, 세상에!
to a dinner party that was
thrown for you, my God!
- 두 시간이라고?
- 그래
- It was two hours?
- Yes.
- 원래 몇신데?
- 7시
- When was dinner?
- 7:00.
7시?
그냥 제안인줄 알았어
7:00? I thought that
was just a suggestion.
제안...여기선
새벽 1시에 밥 안 먹어
A sugges-- Okay, I'm sorry we
don't eat at 1:00 in the morning,
바르셀로나가 아니거든
but we don't live in Barcelona.
1시는 아니고 10시,
그 정돈 괜찮잖아
Maybe not 1:00, but 10:00.
10:00 is reasonable.
봐, 넌 항상 이래,
넌 네 맘대로 하고
See, this is what you do.
You act like I'm uptight,
난 약속을 지키지,
결국 난 꽉막힌 애가 되
and then I follow suit.
I become uptight.
세상에서 가장 짜증나는
논리지
It is the most frustrating
dynamic on the planet.
- 미치겠어, 못 참겠다고
- 젠장, 나 임신했어
- It drives me crazy. I can't stand it.
- I'm fucking pregnant.
알았어?
임신했다고
All right?
I'm pregnant.
- 계획한거야?
- 생각을 해 봐
- On purpose?
- What do you think?
둘 한테
말할게 있어서
I have to tell you
something, you two.
너희들 정말 아름다워
You guys are so beautiful.
좋아, 알았어
Okay, all right.
저게 취한거야
That's a high person.
- 재밌는 글이네, 로린
- 응, 그래
- This is very funny stuff, Loreen.
- Yeah. Uh-huh.
- 하나, 너 참 재밌어
- 고마워요, 아버지
- Hannah, you're a very funny girl.
- Thank you, papa.
- 좋아요
- 오!
- Okay.
- Oh.
원하는 건
딱 하나예요
All I am asking for
책을 완성할 때까지
to finish this book
한 달에
110만원만 주세요
is $1,100 a month
2년 간요
for the next two years.
- 말도 안 되
- 꽤 많구나
- That's insane.
- That's a chunk of change.
엄마는 몰라요,
뉴욕에서 한달에
You would say it's insane.
Who can live in New York
110만원 이라뇨?
on $1,100 a month?
하지만 그만큼
진지하기 때문에
But I am so committed
to this book
이렇게 짜게라도
살겠다는 거예요
that I am willing to get
pretty thrifty on this.
직장은 구하고
블로그에 쓰지 그러니?
Why don't you get a job
and start a blog?
넌 너무
철이 없어
You are so spoiled.
그래요?
그게 누구 잘못이죠, 엄마?
Yeah, well, whose fault
is that, mom?
- 네 아빠 잘못이지
- 정말 심란하구나
- Your father's.
- This is making me so unhappy.
- 기분이 정말 안 좋아
- 우린 은행이 아니야, 하나
- I'm having such a horrible feeling.
- We're not wamu, Hannah.
- 똑바로 앉지 못 하니?
- 하나?
- And the least you can do is sit up straight.
- Hannah?
세상에, 하나!
하나? 하나?
Hannah, Jesus.
Hannah? Hannah?
마시면 안 되는데
기분이 너무 안 좋아서
I shouldn't have taken it, but I
was just having such a bad day.
뭘 마셔?
뭘 마셨어?
Taken what?
What did you take?
쟤 아픈거야?
병원에 전화할까?
Is she sick, Ted?
Do I need to call a hospital?
약에 취한것 같아
I think she may be high.
- 합법이에요, 꽃인데
- 이런, 세상에
- It's legal, like flowers.
- Oh, my God.
화 안 낼게,
궁금해서 그래
I'm not going to be angry.
I'm just really curious.
- 뭘 피웠니?
- 양귀비 씨예요
- What did you smoke?
- It's opium pods.
아편 차예요
It's a tea of opium pods.
- 인터넷에 찾아 볼까?
- 그럴 필요없어
- We should Google that.
- I don't need to Google that.
뭔지 알아,
바나나 껍질 피우는거랑 비슷해
I know about that.
It's tantamount to smoking banana peels.
- 세상에, 커피나 시키자고
- 커피는 어른들거예요
- For Christ's sake, let's just order her a coffee.
- Coffee's for grown-ups.
진한 커피 한잔
마실거야!
You're going to drink
a strong cup of coffee!
난 24살이에요!
명령하지 마요
I'm 24 years old!
Don't tell me what to do.
꼴 진짜 좋네
This is a real display.
아니, 냉담한 교육의
처참한 결과야
No, this is the immediate
result of a cold approach.
- 갑자기 바꾸면 안 된다고
- 왜 이러세요?
- You can't just pull the rug out suddenly.
- Why are you doing this?
몇 일 더 지내야 겠어
We should stay a few more days.
당신의 착한 마음씨는
정말 훌륭하지만
I admire your kind heart,
I really do.
지금 저 망할 사기꾼에게
당하고 있는거야!
But you're getting played
by a major fucking player!
알지만 힘들어하니까
안쓰러워서 그래!
I know! But it's hard for
me to watch her struggle!
치마가 너무
딱 붙어요
My skirt feels so tight.
가위로 잘라줄 수
있어요?
Maybe you can just cut it
open with a scissors?
주사 맞는걸
보는 것 같아!
It's like watching
her get a shot!
주사 맞으면
병이 나아!
Shots keep people from getting sick!
- 호숫가 집을 사려고 열심히 일한다고
- 그래, 알아
- I want a lake house. I work hard.
- I know, I know.
망할 놈의 호숫가에
앉아보고 싶다고
I want to sit
by a fucking lake.
- 당신 그럴 자격있어
- 다락방 플로베어처럼 죽겠다
- You deserve a lake.
- I'm gonna die like Flaubert in a garret.
보지 마요
Don't look at me.
엄마?
Mom?
아빠?
Dad?
2507호 인데요
Hi, I'm in room 2507,
룸서비스 될까요?
and I wanted to get
some room service.
아...
Oh.
체크아웃하면
카드사용 못 해요?
But is the account totally
closed if they've checked out?
더할순 없어요?
You can't add anything?
네, 아뇨,
알았어요
Okay, no.
Yeah, got it.
지금 나갈게요,
고마워요
I'm leaving right now.
Thank you.
좀 웃어봐
Why don't you smile?
상처를 입었나?
Does your heart hurt?
아가씨를 보니
이렇게 말하고 싶네
Girl, when I look at you,
I just wanna say,
"안녕, 뉴욕!"
"Hello, New York!"
♪ Everyone seems so certain ♪
♪ everyone knows who they are ♪
♪ everyone's got a mother
and a father ♪
♪ they all seem so sure
they're going far ♪
♪ I'm as simple as a bee ♪
♪ as a melody in C ♪
♪ but it don't matter ♪
♪ there are more wishes
than stars ♪
♪ every guest so pleased
with themselves ♪
♪ they're brimming
with success ♪
♪ their whole life's
been blessed ♪
♪ but it doesn't matter ♪
♪ everyone's been on
a holiday in the sun ♪
♪ or they just got back
from one ♪
♪ all they do is
just have fun ♪
♪ they all got more friends
than they can use ♪
♪ except me 'cause I'm a fool ♪
♪ I'm simple as a bee ♪
♪ as a melody in C ♪
♪ but it don't matter ♪